# Shawn Conway

Poquoson, VA | 747-200-5084 | conwayshawn33@gmail.com Linkedin | Github | Blog

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Full Stack Web Developer with an ongoing desire for learning. With experience in Python and JavaScript and a background in the Hospitality and Medical Cannabis industries, I bring strong skills in organization, attention to detail, and communication. A passion for problem-solving brought me to web development; my focus and teamwork help drive project completion and a productive work environment.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python with Flask, SQL, JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, API, RESTful routing, Fetch requests, SQLite, Formik, Git, Github, Visual Studio Code, Databases

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## Conway Property Management - Github | Demo

A website that showcases vacation rentals in the Mid-Atlantic area of the United States.

- Utilized flexbox and custom CSS to design frontend
- Incorporated Formik in sign-up form
- Built frontend with React, Flask backend with API endpoints for Fetch requests, and SQLite for data persistence
- Incorporated bcrypt to facilitate custom authentication

### Video Game Library - Github | Demo

An app that allows users to search and select video games and learn which consoles the game is played on.

- Utilized React and Flask to create a full stack website
- Designed using full CRUD
- Created the database schema
- Developed API backend to handle data persistence and respond to fetch requests

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Craft Repair, Hampton, VA

Machinist

09/2022 - 08/2023

- Developed the skills to use a lathe and other machinery in the facility
- Executed Driveshaft and Rim repair
- Communicated with the welding team to ensure parts were repaired correctly for proper installation
- Calculated precise measurements for cutting and shaping materials

### Cannabiotix, Los Angeles, CA

04/2020 - 04/2022

Trimmer

- Delivered 2500 grams of trimmed product in 8 hours on a daily basis; average is usually 300 grams in 8 hours.
- Finished the processing of product before being packaged
- Educated inexperienced trimmers on how to increase productivity

#### Independent Contractor, Los Angeles, CA

04/2012 - 04/2020

Facility Construction and Production Management

- Contributed to the building of cannabis facilities and production of those facilities
- Managed nurseries and flower rooms
- Oversaw the processing of cannabis plants

#### Alta Ski Resort, Alta, UT

11/2009 - 04/2012

Chef at Collins' Grill

- Headed the prep and lunch services
- Created menus and catered events for the resort
- Responsible for inventory and ordering of food and food service supplies.
- Decreased food cost by portion control and consistent production

# **EDUCATION**

# Flatiron School New York, NY

08/2023 - 12/2023

Full Stack Web Development, Python with Flask and JavaScript program